[Applause]
Well, this is a five page introduction, but my son made sure that it's double
spaced and the fun is 18.
[Laughter]
So on behalf of the Bafna, Fennessur and Patel families, I would like to thank
the Cleveland International Hall of Fame for this tremendous honor bestowed
upon our father.
We call my father Kakuza. In our region of India, Kakuza is a respectful title
for father's younger brother.
My father lived in a joint family and since my father is the youngest of three
brothers, all my cousins, his brother's children, called him Kakuza.
As a result, I, my sister and my brother also called him Kakuza.
It is a common occurrence in our village and has continued here at Cleveland as
well.
Kakuza was born to a middle class business family in a small village in
Northwestern State of Rajasan, India.
Though I do not remember much about my grandfather, I do know that he was a
simple man with an iron will, dear him to truth, honesty, compassion and
service to others.
These values have been instilled in Kakuza and he passed them on to his
children, grandchildren and great-granddaughter now.
By sixth grade, Kakuza decided that he wanted to pursue medicine.
Since our village only had a school till seventh grade, he had to be enrolled
and moved to a neighboring village for further studies.
There in eighth grade, he shared an apartment with three boys. They cooked,
cleaned, went to school and studied.
Imagine today sending an eighth grader away from home to live with three other
boys.
Clearly, my grandfather had full confidence in him and Kakuza never let him
down.
He married my mother Kambla when he was 18, was still in medical school and as
the saying goes, behind every successful man, there is a woman.
Kakuza received unconditional love and support from my mother.
She was also a lady of strong will, compassion and of service to the community.
Equipped with scarcely a fifth grade education, for the sake of her family, she
reluctantly agreed to move to the US when she was 31 years old.
She struggled to learn English, to drive and learn ways of her new home. But
she did this with a beautiful smile.
She taught us the meaning of love, respect, kindness, generosity and
hospitality.
Kakuza decided to settle in the US, but he never forgot his roots.
Like his father, he lived a simple life. He continues to give back to his
community in India and his adopted country by building schools and hospitals.
In recognition of his work, the people of his village in India presented him
with their highest honor in front of nearly 10,000 in December of 2014.
He has been a pillar of the Indian community's equipment. He has never said no
to anybody because he is a man of few words.
Yet he walks the walk by delivering his promises.
He is the kind of friend you want in your time of need.
He practiced medicine and bed for nearly 40 years.
He is loved by it, loved and admired by his colleagues, subordinates, and most
of all, his patients.
Kakuza, I have not known a more loving and giving man than you.
You have gave an incredible path for your children, grandchildren and a great
friend of mine.
We are proud of, proud and overjoyed as you receive this honor.
Thank you to all who made this evening possible.
And finally, a special thanks to our extended family in Cleveland and to my
cousin and brother-in-law who came from India for this event.
[applause]
I'm sorry to give you the microphone, but what a testament that people came
from India number one.
And that for the first time ever, the Hall of Fame has a one-year-old in the
end.
They wanted to bring to share this evening.